

ProfessionalPhotographer

PROFILE

Reliable, qualified, and experienced graphic designer working mainly in the IT industry, particularly in software houses. Excellence in creativity, problem-solving, time-management, and technical skills. Offering industrial exposure and providing design solutions for a broad range of webmasters and app developers. Works well with the team of graphic designers, and highly participative in business meetings.

CONTACTME

Phone: +0 012 3456789

Email: youremailhere@gmail.com

Website: www.yourwebsitehere.com

Address: 123-C, Downtown Road, New York, USA

EDUCATION

MASTERSININFORMATIONTECHN OLOGY (2012-2014)

The field of my research in the post-graduation degree was "The role of the efficient interface in medical applications."

BACHELORSINCOMPUTERSCIEN CE(2010-2012)

I had 4.0 CGPA in my undergraduate degree. My project got the first position at the international level that helped me won a gold medal.

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHICDESIGNER(2016-2020)

I Led a team that focused on providing designs to ecommerce websites. Completed most orders in a 6month period and won the perfect designer award.

WEBDESIGNER(2014-2016)

I worked on testing and improving their websites' designs. Worked with different content management systems and prepared plans for website structure and design.

GRAPHICDESIGNER (2012-2014)

I created original graphic designs, including images, sketches, and tables. I've built page navigation buttons and search fields.

SKILLS

ADOBEPHOTOSHOP

ADOBEILLUSTRATOR

ADOBEXD

INDESIGN

FIGMA

SKETCH